nicabm.com 2016-11-27

# National Institute for the Clinical Application of Behavioral Medicine: Privacy Policy - NICABM

****(Last Revised: February 11, 2015)****

Thank you for visiting a NICABM web site, including nicabm.com, mindfulnessforpsychotherapists.com, and webinarsforchange.com. You arrived at this Privacy Policy from one of the above sites, referred to herein as “this web site”.

We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy, and this Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information that is collected at this web site. Please read this Privacy Policy before using this site or submitting any personal information. By using this web site, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. These privacy practices may change from time to time, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the web site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Information We Collect**

In order to serve our customers, we collect personally identifiable information, like names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We may use your personal information and transfer/exchange your personal information for any legal purpose, including, without limitation: (1) to deliver the products and/or services to you that you have requested; (2) to validate your compliance with the terms and conditions; (3) for content improvement and feedback purposes; (4) to reach you, when necessary, regarding your use of the web site or product(s); and (5) to bring retail opportunities and promotional offers to you by email, direct mail, telemarketing, and/or online banner advertising. When your information is provided to third parties, these third parties may include providers of direct marketing services and applications. We or these third parties may supplement the information we collect online with outside records to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and/or to offer you targeted advertising and other opportunities to purchase products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. We will NEVER share your credit card information with third parties unless you have given us explicit permission to do so, such as in order to fulfill a third party offer that you have accepted from us. By permitting us to collect this information, you will be able to receive free information on products and services that may be of interest to you. You also enable us to personalize your experience with us so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service. By submitting your email address on this web site, you agree to receive email from us and our third party advertisers. We, and our third party advertisers, may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do. By submitting your email address, you also allow us to use your email address to display targeted custom audience messages and advertising on sites like Facebook, Pintrest, Twitter, Instagram etc., where we display custom advertising to specific people, like you, who have opted-in to receive communications from us. In addition, you agree that by submitting your email address on this web site and/or registering to receive the product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR ‘310 et seq. and any applicable state and local “do not call” regulations. We and our third party advertisers retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations.

**Third Party Actions**

We do not control and are not liable for the actions of our third party marketers or advertisers. We pride ourselves in working with quality companies, but have no control over the actions of those third parties. While we are not liable for any of the actions of those third parties, you should feel free to give us feedback from time to time on your experiences with any third parties to whom we work with so that we may enhance our future service to all customers.

**Cookies**

We may use cookies to deliver content that is specific to your interests. Cookies are text files that are used by your computer’s web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with our web site. Emails or newsletters that we send electronically may use techniques such as web beacons or pixel tags to gather email metrics and information to improve the reader’s experience, such as the number of emails that are opened, whether they were forwarded or printed, the type of device from which they were opened, and the location (e.g. city, state, and county) associated with the applicable IP address.

**Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting**

We partner with a third party to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by [clicking here](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our websites (through our contact us page) or by e-mail (such as your name and email address). You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website's services and features. 

Any information provided on our website order forms is collected by our payment processing service providers on their servers from Customers who access our site. That information is then shared with NICABM. This information includes ordering information such as shipping and billing names and addresses, phone numbers, email address, and credit card information. We use this information primarily to fulfill customer orders and requests. We do not share this information with any third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law.

**IP Addresses**

We may use your IP address to help prevent fraud, to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and to offer you products and services.

**Third Party Web Sites**

This web site and/or the products and/or services offered herein may direct you to web sites that are owned and/or controlled by third parties. We have no control over those third parties and are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of those sites or companies.

**Commitment to Data Security**

All information collected from you is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. We use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, and we do everything we can to protect user information offline. Unfortunately, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take reasonable measures to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Contacting Us**

If you need to contact us, you can email us at respond@nicabm.com call us at 860-456-1153, or send us a letter at: 40 Wilbur Cross Way, Suite 102, Storrs, CT 06268. We strive to provide excellent products, along with equally excellent customer service. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please feel free to contact us using one of the methods listed above.
